(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me?
(Sheldon:)Isn't this the point
where the world-weary barkeep
(Sheldon:)absentmindedly
wipes down the bar
(Sheldon:)and coaxes the woes
out of the troubled patron?
(Penny:)Well, I was getting your
stupid umbrella, but all right.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)What's troubling you, buddy?
(Sheldon:)I don't think your heart's
in it, but since you asked...
(Sheldon:)Apparently, because
Leonard is dating Raj's sister,
(Sheldon:)we're all forced
to hang out at his apartment.
(Penny:)Oh, the horror.
(Sheldon:)Indeed.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, at one point,
Raj put on reggae music,
(Sheldon:)and his sister
took off her shoes.
(Sheldon:)It was like the last days
of Caligula.
(cell phone chiming)
(Sheldon:)Oh, I have to get this.
(Sheldon:)Umbrella?
(Leonard:)Ugh!
(Sheldon:)Wonder
what she's exasperated about.